hotdeals360.com 2019-03-20

# Privacy Policy - NDTV Gadgets360.com

At Red Pixels Ventures Limited, you always come first. As a result, we do not publish, sell or rent any of your personal data to a third party without your consent.

#### Privacy Policy

We respect and are committed towards protecting your privacy. Publishing, selling or renting any personal data or information to any third party, without your consent, is against our ethic.

For more clarity on how we use and protect your personal information, please go through our privacy policy thoroughly!

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy.

The privacy practices of this statement apply exclusively to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of Red Pixels Ventures Limited and apply generally to our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries or joint venture websites. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our website.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions Agreement while registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance during registration, and is otherwise effective on carrying out any transaction with us for all users.

In the course of registering for and availing various services we provide from time to time through our website (Website, telephone search, SMS and WAP) or any other Media medium in which Red Pixels Ventures Limited may provide services you may be required to disclose your name, residence address, email address, telephone number and similar Personal Information.

The type of information we will collect about you includes:

 _Information We Collect_  
The Personal Information is used for two general purposes: to process your order, and to provide you with the best possible services. Unless otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on any of the Media.

In furtherance of the confidentiality with which we treat Personal Information we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

We use third-party service providers to process purchases you make and to monitor our users' interests. In addition, the Website may occasionally contain links to Third-Party Sites. If you click on the links to Third-Party Websites, you leave the Website. We are not responsible for the content of these Third-Party Websites or for the security of your personal information when you use the Third Party Websites. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. They may collect information such as your IP address, browser specification, or operating system. This Privacy Policy does not govern personal information provided to, stored on, or used by these third-party providers and Third-Party Sites. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Site, you review the Third Party Site's privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to the Website and Third-Party Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don't provide information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail of the our services.

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

 _Mobile Privacy_  
We may offer you the ability for you to connect with our sites, or use our applications, services, and tools using a mobile device, either through a mobile application or via a mobile optimized website. The provisions of this Privacy Policy apply to all such mobile access and use of mobile devices. This Privacy Policy will be referenced by all such mobile applications or mobile optimized websites.

 _Children's Privacy_  
The Red Pixels Ventures Limited's website is a general audience website, and it and its related sites, applications, services, and tools are not intended for children under the age of 18.

 _Your Privacy - Our Commitment_  
Red Pixels Ventures Limited through its website, is extremely proud of its commitment to protect your privacy. We value your trust in us. We will work hard to earn your confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Site.

 _Privacy Guarantee_  
Red Pixels Ventures Limited promises that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. Personal Information may be shared only under one or more of the following circumstances:

(a) If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so;  
(b) If we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so.

Red Pixels Ventures Limited gives you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

While we strive to use a commercially acceptable means to protect the personal information you provide, we cannot guarantee its security. Therefore, you acknowledge and agree that we assume no liability regarding the theft, loss, alteration or misuse of personal or other information or Content, including, without limitation, such information that has been provided to third parties or other users, or with regards to the failure of a third party to abide by the agreement between us and such third party.

Further, you have the right to refuse any marketing email from us or any other trader in the future.

 **Grievance Officer**  
Red Pixels Ventures Limited  
207, Okhla Industrial Estate, Phase III,  
New Delhi - 110020
